Quantity spared, Yatin, tell me, there are chances in Europe.
What was Ahmed saying here? All the
brokerages have given in this. Most of the
brokerages, as we are talking, have set
target prices. Okay, in the
quarter-four results, there was
quality due to fruit, but the
consumer business, especially Reliance Retail
and Reliance Jio,
we have increased the target in points due to fielding.
With Axis Capital, their target is
1780. This means that it is on the front side.
They have said that we have a strong
reception, which is subscribed on the positive side.
Now there are changes in the skin, in
one teaspoon, this is the victory of Congress.
They have increased the target price by ₹100. The
new target is 1720. Apart from this,
Bank of America Merrill Lynch says that the
commentary on the rights issue of fiction
overshadows the entire Q4 results and the subsequent
commentary is tremendous. The target is 0.0, they
thought right, but the target came higher and the
rights are positive, then there is a festival.  This is the
problem but you
must subscribe to this, if you
subscribe to your topic then it
means that this business has got more than fifty percent
resolution and subscribe to
your retail audio, you have done a lot of research work,
which he has also appointed Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal.